things she asked me right there
and so. But otherwise I don't remember
very much so. But I was by myself
pensive
because of what had happened recently
the months itself if it was the right time to
marry or not. So there arose one
other reasons were.
I don't know if I have received an answer
the. Gustav,
>> now please specify what it was
as
uh you thought about there because I I
I'm also a little unsure myself.
expressed yet to her directly but that
she could still feel it on something
maybe use body language and stuff like that
>> so it also affected the judgment but
absolutely it was clumsy.
>> Mmm. You also send clips of yours
conversations. Eh